她刚刚只试了一次发球 就停下了
把时间拨回30分钟前
北京时间8月21日早上7点前
辛辛那提女单四分之一决赛
世界第2莱巴金娜
对世界第5斯瓦泰克
萨巴伦卡已经出局
她只要再赢两场打进决赛
就能在美网开始前
第一次成为世界第1
5局之后 斯瓦泰克4比1领先
总分22比14
莱巴金娜制胜分5比4更多
非受迫失误却是8比4
第六局 莱巴金娜发球
30比40
她救回破发点
追到40平
接下来这100多秒 完整保留
Couldn't pick up the half-volley.
半截击没能处理好
What just happened?
刚才发生了什么
Yeah, I think she hurt her leg on that previous point.
我想她是在上一分伤到了腿
Her Achilles.
是她的跟腱
She's got tape on her left ankle.
她的左脚踝贴着胶布
Rybakina has requested the physio mid-game, at 4 比 1, deuce, serving.
莱巴金娜在1比4平分的发球局请求理疗师入场
You see the bit of tape on her left ankle, heel.
可以看到她左脚踝和脚跟处的胶布
Not moving comfortably at all.
她走路明显很不舒服
Her team has to look on here, but Brett, if it is the Achilles...
她的团队只能在场边看着 但如果真是跟腱……
Here's the fact: Rybakina is two wins away from the No. 1 ranking.
事实是 莱巴金娜距离世界第一只差两场胜利
If she wins this and then wins the semi,
如果她赢下这场 再赢下半决赛
she will supplant Sabalenka by exactly one point
她将以恰好一分的优势取代萨巴伦卡
and become the world No. 1 for the first time.
并首次登上世界第一
It doesn't look great here. She hasn't looked that comfortable.
情况看起来不妙 她一直很不舒服
She retired from a tournament just once earlier this year.
她今年此前只退赛过一次
No power on the serve at all.
这次发球完全没有力量
Yeah, that's it. She's done.
是的 到此为止了 她打不了了
She's going to call it, and that is a shame.
她要宣布退赛了 这太遗憾了
WTA账上是31分18秒
盘内净打26分17秒
多出来的五分钟
就是这次治疗和离场
斯瓦泰克晋级 对佩古拉
莱巴金娜错过美网前登顶
她走回底线 试过继续
10天后 美网见吗？